{"question":"808 - 300 = ?","answers":[{"value":"508", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"725 - 493 = ?","answers":[{"value":"232", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"766 - 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"702", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"902 - 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"854", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"537 + 274 = ?","answers":[{"value":"811", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"629 - 11 = ?","answers":[{"value":"618", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"604 - 465 = ?","answers":[{"value":"139", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17 + 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"38", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"661 - 555 = ?","answers":[{"value":"106", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"803 - 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"788", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74 + 2 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"783 - 407 = ?","answers":[{"value":"376", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"704 - 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"670", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"338 + 245 = ?","answers":[{"value":"583", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74 + 230 = ?","answers":[{"value":"304", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"503 - 160 = ?","answers":[{"value":"343", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"581 - 178 = ?","answers":[{"value":"403", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"10 + 11 = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"906 - 500 = ?","answers":[{"value":"406", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77 + 655 = ?","answers":[{"value":"732", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"859 - 211 = ?","answers":[{"value":"648", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"600 - 166 = ?","answers":[{"value":"434", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17 + 409 = ?","answers":[{"value":"426", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"562 - 261 = ?","answers":[{"value":"301", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"902 - 1 = ?","answers":[{"value":"901", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"436 - 331 = ?","answers":[{"value":"105", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99 + 375 = ?","answers":[{"value":"474", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"709 - 169 = ?","answers":[{"value":"540", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"256 + 177 = ?","answers":[{"value":"433", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"754 - 582 = ?","answers":[{"value":"172", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"900 - 13 = ?","answers":[{"value":"887", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"865 - 201 = ?","answers":[{"value":"664", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"322 + 335 = ?","answers":[{"value":"657", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"909 - 84 = ?","answers":[{"value":"825", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"601 + 95 = ?","answers":[{"value":"696", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"796 - 382 = ?","answers":[{"value":"414", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"901 - 96 = ?","answers":[{"value":"805", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"809 + 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"873", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"21 + 246 = ?","answers":[{"value":"267", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"908 - 399 = ?","answers":[{"value":"509", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"669 - 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"627", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"447 + 14 = ?","answers":[{"value":"461", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"901 - 492 = ?","answers":[{"value":"409", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"897 - 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"880", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"521 - 228 = ?","answers":[{"value":"293", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"409 - 223 = ?","answers":[{"value":"186", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"537 + 180 = ?","answers":[{"value":"717", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75 + 12 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"907 - 239 = ?","answers":[{"value":"668", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"816 - 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"787", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"637 + 10 = ?","answers":[{"value":"647", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"405 - 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"332", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"124 + 91 = ?","answers":[{"value":"215", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"419 + 342 = ?","answers":[{"value":"761", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"803 - 446 = ?","answers":[{"value":"357", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"32 + 250 = ?","answers":[{"value":"282", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"817 - 249 = ?","answers":[{"value":"568", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"505 - 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"430", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"71 + 86 = ?","answers":[{"value":"157", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"689 - 262 = ?","answers":[{"value":"427", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"900 - 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"852", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"420 + 431 = ?","answers":[{"value":"851", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"899 - 187 = ?","answers":[{"value":"712", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"504 - 120 = ?","answers":[{"value":"384", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"264 + 572 = ?","answers":[{"value":"836", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"555 - 547 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"800 - 617 = ?","answers":[{"value":"183", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"594 - 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"579", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"751 - 569 = ?","answers":[{"value":"182", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"904 - 262 = ?","answers":[{"value":"642", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"18 + 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"38", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"623 + 222 = ?","answers":[{"value":"845", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"906 - 325 = ?","answers":[{"value":"581", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"125 + 675 = ?","answers":[{"value":"800", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"544 - 514 = ?","answers":[{"value":"30", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"809 - 250 = ?","answers":[{"value":"559", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"520 + 168 = ?","answers":[{"value":"688", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"241 + 315 = ?","answers":[{"value":"556", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"401 - 13 = ?","answers":[{"value":"388", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"710 + 146 = ?","answers":[{"value":"856", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"891 - 316 = ?","answers":[{"value":"575", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"404 - 114 = ?","answers":[{"value":"290", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"673 - 311 = ?","answers":[{"value":"362", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"679 + 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"757", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"401 - 150 = ?","answers":[{"value":"251", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"835 - 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"775", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"526 - 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"484", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"908 - 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"882", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"273 - 213 = ?","answers":[{"value":"60", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"642 + 175 = ?","answers":[{"value":"817", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"702 - 467 = ?","answers":[{"value":"235", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"818 - 436 = ?","answers":[{"value":"382", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"496 - 91 = ?","answers":[{"value":"405", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"907 - 441 = ?","answers":[{"value":"466", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"147 + 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"166", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"759 - 607 = ?","answers":[{"value":"152", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"609 - 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"537", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"444 - 12 = ?","answers":[{"value":"432", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"811 - 97 = ?","answers":[{"value":"714", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"902 - 93 = ?","answers":[{"value":"809", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"825 - 484 = ?","answers":[{"value":"341", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"480 + 192 = ?","answers":[{"value":"672", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"809 - 217 = ?","answers":[{"value":"592", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"435 + 248 = ?","answers":[{"value":"683", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 + 12 = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"902 - 567 = ?","answers":[{"value":"335", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"11 + 414 = ?","answers":[{"value":"425", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"533 - 325 = ?","answers":[{"value":"208", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"804 - 286 = ?","answers":[{"value":"518", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"168 + 251 = ?","answers":[{"value":"419", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"82 + 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"146", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"707 - 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"667", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"624 + 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"687", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"510 + 346 = ?","answers":[{"value":"856", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"705 - 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"625", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"154 + 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"222", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"22 + 472 = ?","answers":[{"value":"494", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"609 - 404 = ?","answers":[{"value":"205", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"85 + 177 = ?","answers":[{"value":"262", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"897 - 151 = ?","answers":[{"value":"746", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"904 - 117 = ?","answers":[{"value":"787", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"576 + 92 = ?","answers":[{"value":"668", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"553 - 291 = ?","answers":[{"value":"262", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"505 - 220 = ?","answers":[{"value":"285", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"516 - 463 = ?","answers":[{"value":"53", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"148 + 751 = ?","answers":[{"value":"899", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"608 - 5 = ?","answers":[{"value":"603", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"585 - 338 = ?","answers":[{"value":"247", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"892 + 13 = ?","answers":[{"value":"905", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"602 - 436 = ?","answers":[{"value":"166", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"144 + 129 = ?","answers":[{"value":"273", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"887 - 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"848", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"905 - 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"856", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"481 - 281 = ?","answers":[{"value":"200", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"238 + 346 = ?","answers":[{"value":"584", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"709 - 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"662", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"861 - 8 = ?","answers":[{"value":"853", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"465 + 418 = ?","answers":[{"value":"883", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"708 - 440 = ?","answers":[{"value":"268", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"143 + 538 = ?","answers":[{"value":"681", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"664 - 2 = ?","answers":[{"value":"662", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"906 - 820 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"175 + 381 = ?","answers":[{"value":"556", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"741 - 399 = ?","answers":[{"value":"342", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"908 - 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"859", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"145 + 373 = ?","answers":[{"value":"518", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"772 - 576 = ?","answers":[{"value":"196", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"703 - 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"625", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"534 - 126 = ?","answers":[{"value":"408", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"14 + 144 = ?","answers":[{"value":"158", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"900 - 223 = ?","answers":[{"value":"677", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99 + 502 = ?","answers":[{"value":"601", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"587 - 117 = ?","answers":[{"value":"470", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"502 - 171 = ?","answers":[{"value":"331", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"552 + 222 = ?","answers":[{"value":"774", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"476 + 352 = ?","answers":[{"value":"828", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"509 - 154 = ?","answers":[{"value":"355", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"155 + 149 = ?","answers":[{"value":"304", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"692 + 92 = ?","answers":[{"value":"784", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"606 - 503 = ?","answers":[{"value":"103", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"737 - 119 = ?","answers":[{"value":"618", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"564 + 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"611", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"706 - 336 = ?","answers":[{"value":"370", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"721 - 243 = ?","answers":[{"value":"478", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"835 - 146 = ?","answers":[{"value":"689", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"803 - 111 = ?","answers":[{"value":"692", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"167 + 210 = ?","answers":[{"value":"377", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"505 + 98 = ?","answers":[{"value":"603", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"307 - 251 = ?","answers":[{"value":"56", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"736 - 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"717", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"851 - 207 = ?","answers":[{"value":"644", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"905 - 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"865", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"92 - 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"62", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"787 - 357 = ?","answers":[{"value":"430", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"902 - 881 = ?","answers":[{"value":"21", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"430 - 174 = ?","answers":[{"value":"256", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"292 - 171 = ?","answers":[{"value":"121", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"205 - 114 = ?","answers":[{"value":"91", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97 + 241 = ?","answers":[{"value":"338", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"856 - 196 = ?","answers":[{"value":"660", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102 - 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"552 + 143 = ?","answers":[{"value":"695", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"749 - 110 = ?","answers":[{"value":"639", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"907 - 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"829", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"208 + 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"243", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"576 - 106 = ?","answers":[{"value":"470", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"408 - 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"329", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90 + 169 = ?","answers":[{"value":"259", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"321 + 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"357", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"705 - 82 = ?","answers":[{"value":"623", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"747 - 739 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"491 + 93 = ?","answers":[{"value":"584", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"905 - 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"870", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"756 - 481 = ?","answers":[{"value":"275", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"524 - 190 = ?","answers":[{"value":"334", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"800 - 275 = ?","answers":[{"value":"525", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"775 - 575 = ?","answers":[{"value":"200", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"357 - 313 = ?","answers":[{"value":"44", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"909 - 721 = ?","answers":[{"value":"188", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"578 - 403 = ?","answers":[{"value":"175", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"656 + 227 = ?","answers":[{"value":"883", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"704 - 250 = ?","answers":[{"value":"454", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"321 + 473 = ?","answers":[{"value":"794", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15 + 796 = ?","answers":[{"value":"811", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"803 - 251 = ?","answers":[{"value":"552", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"424 + 95 = ?","answers":[{"value":"519", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"61 + 398 = ?","answers":[{"value":"459", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"209 - 165 = ?","answers":[{"value":"44", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"134 + 742 = ?","answers":[{"value":"876", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19 + 6 = ?","answers":[{"value":"25", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"904 - 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"828", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"125 - 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"54", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"814 - 586 = ?","answers":[{"value":"228", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"705 - 170 = ?","answers":[{"value":"535", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101 + 120 = ?","answers":[{"value":"221", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"885 - 9 = ?","answers":[{"value":"876", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"704 - 481 = ?","answers":[{"value":"223", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"718 - 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"683", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76 + 642 = ?","answers":[{"value":"718", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108 - 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"82", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"413 - 368 = ?","answers":[{"value":"45", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"357 + 395 = ?","answers":[{"value":"752", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"708 - 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"652", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"477 + 83 = ?","answers":[{"value":"560", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68 + 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"105", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"906 - 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"876", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"328 + 222 = ?","answers":[{"value":"550", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"528 + 82 = ?","answers":[{"value":"610", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"405 - 126 = ?","answers":[{"value":"279", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 + 362 = ?","answers":[{"value":"435", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"28 - 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"606 - 237 = ?","answers":[{"value":"369", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"687 - 277 = ?","answers":[{"value":"410", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"862 - 105 = ?","answers":[{"value":"757", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"809 - 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"738", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"136 + 259 = ?","answers":[{"value":"395", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"767 - 6 = ?","answers":[{"value":"761", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"807 - 199 = ?","answers":[{"value":"608", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"784 - 742 = ?","answers":[{"value":"42", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"352 - 276 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106 - 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"65", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"505 + 171 = ?","answers":[{"value":"676", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"267 - 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"200", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"904 - 275 = ?","answers":[{"value":"629", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"427 + 134 = ?","answers":[{"value":"561", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"27 + 775 = ?","answers":[{"value":"802", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"905 - 416 = ?","answers":[{"value":"489", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54 + 555 = ?","answers":[{"value":"609", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"434 + 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"449", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"901 - 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"857", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"200 + 639 = ?","answers":[{"value":"839", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"41 + 541 = ?","answers":[{"value":"582", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"802 - 246 = ?","answers":[{"value":"556", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"824 - 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"797", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"882 - 82 = ?","answers":[{"value":"800", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"602 - 334 = ?","answers":[{"value":"268", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 + 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"45", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"521 + 14 = ?","answers":[{"value":"535", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"906 - 248 = ?","answers":[{"value":"658", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"511 - 483 = ?","answers":[{"value":"28", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"283 + 120 = ?","answers":[{"value":"403", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"909 - 196 = ?","answers":[{"value":"713", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47 + 614 = ?","answers":[{"value":"661", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65 + 835 = ?","answers":[{"value":"900", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100 - 83 = ?","answers":[{"value":"17", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"533 + 204 = ?","answers":[{"value":"737", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"860 - 434 = ?","answers":[{"value":"426", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"801 - 8 = ?","answers":[{"value":"793", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"895 - 7 = ?","answers":[{"value":"888", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"743 + 2 = ?","answers":[{"value":"745", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"806 - 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"781", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"157 + 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"208", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"665 - 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"614", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"806 - 117 = ?","answers":[{"value":"689", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"119 + 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"193", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"128 + 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"161", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"902 - 640 = ?","answers":[{"value":"262", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"386 + 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"405", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"562 + 270 = ?","answers":[{"value":"832", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"609 - 90 = ?","answers":[{"value":"519", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"257 - 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"241", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 + 640 = ?","answers":[{"value":"644", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"707 - 645 = ?","answers":[{"value":"62", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"782 + 81 = ?","answers":[{"value":"863", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 + 631 = ?","answers":[{"value":"701", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"805 - 327 = ?","answers":[{"value":"478", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"845 - 604 = ?","answers":[{"value":"241", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"510 + 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"548", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"802 - 13 = ?","answers":[{"value":"789", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"396 - 223 = ?","answers":[{"value":"173", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"441 + 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"476", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"903 - 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"828", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"881 - 693 = ?","answers":[{"value":"188", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 + 3 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"902 - 645 = ?","answers":[{"value":"257", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"569 - 186 = ?","answers":[{"value":"383", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"897 - 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"850", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"808 - 663 = ?","answers":[{"value":"145", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"194 + 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"211", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"884 - 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"838", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"902 - 443 = ?","answers":[{"value":"459", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 + 382 = ?","answers":[{"value":"385", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"714 - 490 = ?","answers":[{"value":"224", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"801 - 644 = ?","answers":[{"value":"157", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"812 - 643 = ?","answers":[{"value":"169", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"365 + 292 = ?","answers":[{"value":"657", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"606 - 250 = ?","answers":[{"value":"356", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45 + 269 = ?","answers":[{"value":"314", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54 + 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"302 - 119 = ?","answers":[{"value":"183", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"495 + 310 = ?","answers":[{"value":"805", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"828 - 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"809", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"800 - 448 = ?","answers":[{"value":"352", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"719 - 139 = ?","answers":[{"value":"580", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26 + 484 = ?","answers":[{"value":"510", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"206 - 87 = ?","answers":[{"value":"119", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"654 - 8 = ?","answers":[{"value":"646", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75 + 355 = ?","answers":[{"value":"430", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"500 - 454 = ?","answers":[{"value":"46", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"121 + 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"174", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"376 - 231 = ?","answers":[{"value":"145", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"800 - 209 = ?","answers":[{"value":"591", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"476 + 254 = ?","answers":[{"value":"730", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"510 - 131 = ?","answers":[{"value":"379", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"907 - 260 = ?","answers":[{"value":"647", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"94 + 136 = ?","answers":[{"value":"230", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"187 + 12 = ?","answers":[{"value":"199", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"904 - 888 = ?","answers":[{"value":"16", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"653 - 300 = ?","answers":[{"value":"353", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"899 - 14 = ?","answers":[{"value":"885", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"800 - 645 = ?","answers":[{"value":"155", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"721 - 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"645", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"559 - 483 = ?","answers":[{"value":"76", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"806 - 285 = ?","answers":[{"value":"521", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"24 + 301 = ?","answers":[{"value":"325", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"398 - 143 = ?","answers":[{"value":"255", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"805 - 244 = ?","answers":[{"value":"561", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"694 - 473 = ?","answers":[{"value":"221", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"378 + 362 = ?","answers":[{"value":"740", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"902 - 125 = ?","answers":[{"value":"777", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74 + 269 = ?","answers":[{"value":"343", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17 + 268 = ?","answers":[{"value":"285", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"801 - 390 = ?","answers":[{"value":"411", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"626 - 309 = ?","answers":[{"value":"317", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"87 + 779 = ?","answers":[{"value":"866", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"904 - 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"873", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"323 + 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"382", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"474 + 323 = ?","answers":[{"value":"797", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"400 - 240 = ?","answers":[{"value":"160", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55 + 280 = ?","answers":[{"value":"335", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15 + 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"34", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"403 - 278 = ?","answers":[{"value":"125", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"160 + 517 = ?","answers":[{"value":"677", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"813 - 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"796", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"601 - 237 = ?","answers":[{"value":"364", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"776 - 186 = ?","answers":[{"value":"590", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"587 - 149 = ?","answers":[{"value":"438", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"901 - 653 = ?","answers":[{"value":"248", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"731 - 108 = ?","answers":[{"value":"623", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"559 + 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"611", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"903 - 125 = ?","answers":[{"value":"778", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"435 - 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"397", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"512 - 302 = ?","answers":[{"value":"210", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"900 - 587 = ?","answers":[{"value":"313", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"95 + 168 = ?","answers":[{"value":"263", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"769 - 280 = ?","answers":[{"value":"489", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"409 - 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"354", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"711 - 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"667", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"10 + 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"62", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"302 - 224 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"448 - 260 = ?","answers":[{"value":"188", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"287 + 82 = ?","answers":[{"value":"369", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"902 - 321 = ?","answers":[{"value":"581", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78 + 499 = ?","answers":[{"value":"577", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"329 - 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"300", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"709 - 93 = ?","answers":[{"value":"616", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"259 + 14 = ?","answers":[{"value":"273", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"127 + 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"166", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"301 - 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"245", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"681 - 85 = ?","answers":[{"value":"596", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"853 - 302 = ?","answers":[{"value":"551", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"405 - 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"347", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"479 - 256 = ?","answers":[{"value":"223", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90 + 504 = ?","answers":[{"value":"594", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"802 - 184 = ?","answers":[{"value":"618", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"129 + 257 = ?","answers":[{"value":"386", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"617 - 90 = ?","answers":[{"value":"527", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"906 - 388 = ?","answers":[{"value":"518", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"364 + 9 = ?","answers":[{"value":"373", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"539 + 362 = ?","answers":[{"value":"901", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"602 - 263 = ?","answers":[{"value":"339", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"510 + 287 = ?","answers":[{"value":"797", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"124 + 440 = ?","answers":[{"value":"564", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"305 - 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"264", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"680 - 99 = ?","answers":[{"value":"581", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"653 - 296 = ?","answers":[{"value":"357", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"908 - 348 = ?","answers":[{"value":"560", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"751 - 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"674", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"280 + 117 = ?","answers":[{"value":"397", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"804 - 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"744", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"712 + 193 = ?","answers":[{"value":"905", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"434 - 142 = ?","answers":[{"value":"292", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"909 - 7 = ?","answers":[{"value":"902", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"345 + 268 = ?","answers":[{"value":"613", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"872 - 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"843", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"806 - 194 = ?","answers":[{"value":"612", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"228 + 284 = ?","answers":[{"value":"512", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"285 + 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"349", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"904 - 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"837", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"536 - 101 = ?","answers":[{"value":"435", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"884 - 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"823", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"303 - 116 = ?","answers":[{"value":"187", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102 + 279 = ?","answers":[{"value":"381", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"11 + 8 = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"705 - 262 = ?","answers":[{"value":"443", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"769 - 690 = ?","answers":[{"value":"79", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 - 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"25", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"909 - 318 = ?","answers":[{"value":"591", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"499 + 158 = ?","answers":[{"value":"657", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 + 2 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"904 - 2 = ?","answers":[{"value":"902", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"425 + 260 = ?","answers":[{"value":"685", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75 + 125 = ?","answers":[{"value":"200", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"903 - 792 = ?","answers":[{"value":"111", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"654 - 166 = ?","answers":[{"value":"488", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"820 - 511 = ?","answers":[{"value":"309", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"904 - 125 = ?","answers":[{"value":"779", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97 + 179 = ?","answers":[{"value":"276", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"675 - 255 = ?","answers":[{"value":"420", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"908 - 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"831", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"892 - 12 = ?","answers":[{"value":"880", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"887 - 155 = ?","answers":[{"value":"732", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"703 - 348 = ?","answers":[{"value":"355", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"756 - 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"693", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"669 - 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"622", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"800 - 90 = ?","answers":[{"value":"710", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"18 + 148 = ?","answers":[{"value":"166", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"217 + 432 = ?","answers":[{"value":"649", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"801 - 108 = ?","answers":[{"value":"693", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"882 - 8 = ?","answers":[{"value":"874", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"546 + 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"583", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"509 - 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"482", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"738 - 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"708", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"895 - 122 = ?","answers":[{"value":"773", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"606 - 171 = ?","answers":[{"value":"435", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"284 + 314 = ?","answers":[{"value":"598", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76 + 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"142", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"903 - 185 = ?","answers":[{"value":"718", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"110 + 258 = ?","answers":[{"value":"368", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"196 + 299 = ?","answers":[{"value":"495", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"909 - 336 = ?","answers":[{"value":"573", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"898 - 426 = ?","answers":[{"value":"472", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 + 777 = ?","answers":[{"value":"833", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"601 - 151 = ?","answers":[{"value":"450", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"226 + 98 = ?","answers":[{"value":"324", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"415 - 189 = ?","answers":[{"value":"226", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"807 - 187 = ?","answers":[{"value":"620", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"155 + 200 = ?","answers":[{"value":"355", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"131 + 192 = ?","answers":[{"value":"323", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"701 - 11 = ?","answers":[{"value":"690", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"881 - 582 = ?","answers":[{"value":"299", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"611 - 5 = ?","answers":[{"value":"606", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"606 - 335 = ?","answers":[{"value":"271", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"541 + 202 = ?","answers":[{"value":"743", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"849 - 273 = ?","answers":[{"value":"576", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"905 - 324 = ?","answers":[{"value":"581", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"383 + 228 = ?","answers":[{"value":"611", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"769 - 144 = ?","answers":[{"value":"625", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"902 - 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"825", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"214 + 533 = ?","answers":[{"value":"747", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"295 + 318 = ?","answers":[{"value":"613", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"908 - 386 = ?","answers":[{"value":"522", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"671 - 382 = ?","answers":[{"value":"289", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"440 + 404 = ?","answers":[{"value":"844", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"402 - 340 = ?","answers":[{"value":"62", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"440 + 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"503", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"451 - 245 = ?","answers":[{"value":"206", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"801 - 530 = ?","answers":[{"value":"271", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"153 + 89 = ?","answers":[{"value":"242", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"29 + 528 = ?","answers":[{"value":"557", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"904 - 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"871", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"87 + 213 = ?","answers":[{"value":"300", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"152 + 695 = ?","answers":[{"value":"847", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"904 - 4 = ?","answers":[{"value":"900", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"31 + 276 = ?","answers":[{"value":"307", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"88 + 814 = ?","answers":[{"value":"902", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"900 - 373 = ?","answers":[{"value":"527", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"332 - 126 = ?","answers":[{"value":"206", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"416 + 196 = ?","answers":[{"value":"612", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"503 - 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"437", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"196 + 392 = ?","answers":[{"value":"588", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"678 - 653 = ?","answers":[{"value":"25", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"908 - 703 = ?","answers":[{"value":"205", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"783 - 2 = ?","answers":[{"value":"781", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"332 - 314 = ?","answers":[{"value":"18", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"701 - 668 = ?","answers":[{"value":"33", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"772 - 690 = ?","answers":[{"value":"82", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"279 - 202 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"908 - 851 = ?","answers":[{"value":"57", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"424 - 182 = ?","answers":[{"value":"242", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"16 + 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"68", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"801 - 568 = ?","answers":[{"value":"233", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"291 + 201 = ?","answers":[{"value":"492", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"500 + 278 = ?","answers":[{"value":"778", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"400 - 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"333", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"256 + 548 = ?","answers":[{"value":"804", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 + 131 = ?","answers":[{"value":"190", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"601 - 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"564", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 + 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99 + 157 = ?","answers":[{"value":"256", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"901 - 282 = ?","answers":[{"value":"619", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"821 - 101 = ?","answers":[{"value":"720", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"883 - 674 = ?","answers":[{"value":"209", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"306 - 234 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"281 + 181 = ?","answers":[{"value":"462", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"691 - 127 = ?","answers":[{"value":"564", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"506 - 292 = ?","answers":[{"value":"214", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"536 - 503 = ?","answers":[{"value":"33", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"874 - 410 = ?","answers":[{"value":"464", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"907 - 171 = ?","answers":[{"value":"736", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"210 + 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"225", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"857 - 610 = ?","answers":[{"value":"247", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"803 - 270 = ?","answers":[{"value":"533", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"533 - 294 = ?","answers":[{"value":"239", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"181 + 708 = ?","answers":[{"value":"889", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"705 - 158 = ?","answers":[{"value":"547", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"155 + 215 = ?","answers":[{"value":"370", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15 + 268 = ?","answers":[{"value":"283", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"308 - 107 = ?","answers":[{"value":"201", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15 + 202 = ?","answers":[{"value":"217", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"697 - 277 = ?","answers":[{"value":"420", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"907 - 491 = ?","answers":[{"value":"416", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"242 - 177 = ?","answers":[{"value":"65", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"887 - 327 = ?","answers":[{"value":"560", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"702 - 183 = ?","answers":[{"value":"519", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"430 - 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"379", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"896 - 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"873", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"906 - 128 = ?","answers":[{"value":"778", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"851 - 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"822", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"777 - 343 = ?","answers":[{"value":"434", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"700 - 96 = ?","answers":[{"value":"604", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"491 - 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"457", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"592 + 202 = ?","answers":[{"value":"794", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"302 - 94 = ?","answers":[{"value":"208", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"275 + 13 = ?","answers":[{"value":"288", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"331 + 84 = ?","answers":[{"value":"415", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"804 - 400 = ?","answers":[{"value":"404", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"896 - 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"847", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"846 - 480 = ?","answers":[{"value":"366", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"703 - 419 = ?","answers":[{"value":"284", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"349 - 109 = ?","answers":[{"value":"240", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"456 + 123 = ?","answers":[{"value":"579", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"302 - 130 = ?","answers":[{"value":"172", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"135 + 492 = ?","answers":[{"value":"627", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"849 - 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"821", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"601 - 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"562", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"217 + 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"257", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"887 - 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"861", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"802 - 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"781", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"411 + 343 = ?","answers":[{"value":"754", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"894 - 392 = ?","answers":[{"value":"502", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"905 - 87 = ?","answers":[{"value":"818", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"319 + 151 = ?","answers":[{"value":"470", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 + 493 = ?","answers":[{"value":"498", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"602 - 317 = ?","answers":[{"value":"285", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"887 - 117 = ?","answers":[{"value":"770", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"141 + 151 = ?","answers":[{"value":"292", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"907 - 294 = ?","answers":[{"value":"613", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"171 + 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"207", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37 + 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"57", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"309 - 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"233", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 + 308 = ?","answers":[{"value":"317", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"125 + 527 = ?","answers":[{"value":"652", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"709 - 233 = ?","answers":[{"value":"476", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"676 - 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"627", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"895 - 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"866", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"709 - 403 = ?","answers":[{"value":"306", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104 + 213 = ?","answers":[{"value":"317", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"875 - 197 = ?","answers":[{"value":"678", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"607 - 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"562", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"179 + 138 = ?","answers":[{"value":"317", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"882 - 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"803", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"406 - 183 = ?","answers":[{"value":"223", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"260 + 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"311", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109 + 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"141", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"900 - 3 = ?","answers":[{"value":"897", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"392 - 354 = ?","answers":[{"value":"38", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"603 + 94 = ?","answers":[{"value":"697", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"905 - 680 = ?","answers":[{"value":"225", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"860 - 563 = ?","answers":[{"value":"297", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"623 - 96 = ?","answers":[{"value":"527", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"906 - 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"838", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"853 - 178 = ?","answers":[{"value":"675", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"368 - 360 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"904 - 155 = ?","answers":[{"value":"749", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"589 - 334 = ?","answers":[{"value":"255", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"792 - 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"774", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"800 - 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"743", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"390 + 449 = ?","answers":[{"value":"839", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"871 - 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"791", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"808 - 103 = ?","answers":[{"value":"705", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"560 - 86 = ?","answers":[{"value":"474", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"777 + 101 = ?","answers":[{"value":"878", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"604 - 403 = ?","answers":[{"value":"201", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"265 + 530 = ?","answers":[{"value":"795", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"589 + 164 = ?","answers":[{"value":"753", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"904 - 368 = ?","answers":[{"value":"536", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"578 - 166 = ?","answers":[{"value":"412", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"754 - 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"736", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"806 - 356 = ?","answers":[{"value":"450", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"14 + 143 = ?","answers":[{"value":"157", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"165 + 179 = ?","answers":[{"value":"344", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"409 - 1 = ?","answers":[{"value":"408", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"665 - 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"606", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"590 - 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"513", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"202 - 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"174", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"194 + 646 = ?","answers":[{"value":"840", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"899 - 3 = ?","answers":[{"value":"896", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"801 - 603 = ?","answers":[{"value":"198", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"582 - 120 = ?","answers":[{"value":"462", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"458 + 349 = ?","answers":[{"value":"807", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"905 - 539 = ?","answers":[{"value":"366", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"233 + 292 = ?","answers":[{"value":"525", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"594 + 287 = ?","answers":[{"value":"881", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"708 - 305 = ?","answers":[{"value":"403", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"749 - 270 = ?","answers":[{"value":"479", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"573 - 96 = ?","answers":[{"value":"477", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"509 - 229 = ?","answers":[{"value":"280", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"528 - 191 = ?","answers":[{"value":"337", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"865 - 1 = ?","answers":[{"value":"864", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"708 - 99 = ?","answers":[{"value":"609", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"595 + 114 = ?","answers":[{"value":"709", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"472 + 250 = ?","answers":[{"value":"722", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"801 - 14 = ?","answers":[{"value":"787", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"161 + 187 = ?","answers":[{"value":"348", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"33 + 3 = ?","answers":[{"value":"36", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"900 - 192 = ?","answers":[{"value":"708", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101 + 134 = ?","answers":[{"value":"235", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"267 + 387 = ?","answers":[{"value":"654", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"904 - 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"855", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"421 - 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"356", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"569 - 268 = ?","answers":[{"value":"301", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"906 - 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"885", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"117 + 185 = ?","answers":[{"value":"302", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 + 88 = ?","answers":[{"value":"150", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"706 - 419 = ?","answers":[{"value":"287", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"719 - 129 = ?","answers":[{"value":"590", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51 + 191 = ?","answers":[{"value":"242", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"702 - 415 = ?","answers":[{"value":"287", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"854 + 10 = ?","answers":[{"value":"864", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"664 - 211 = ?","answers":[{"value":"453", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"500 - 118 = ?","answers":[{"value":"382", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"771 - 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"698", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"240 - 167 = ?","answers":[{"value":"73", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"806 - 329 = ?","answers":[{"value":"477", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"464 + 432 = ?","answers":[{"value":"896", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"351 + 429 = ?","answers":[{"value":"780", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"702 - 350 = ?","answers":[{"value":"352", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"156 + 11 = ?","answers":[{"value":"167", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"537 - 503 = ?","answers":[{"value":"34", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"908 - 94 = ?","answers":[{"value":"814", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 + 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"94", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"83 + 168 = ?","answers":[{"value":"251", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"705 - 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"668", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"457 - 161 = ?","answers":[{"value":"296", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"193 + 14 = ?","answers":[{"value":"207", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"904 - 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"853", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"371 + 252 = ?","answers":[{"value":"623", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20 + 90 = ?","answers":[{"value":"110", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"506 - 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"451", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"237 + 185 = ?","answers":[{"value":"422", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"614 - 533 = ?","answers":[{"value":"81", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"900 - 83 = ?","answers":[{"value":"817", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"658 - 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"628", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63 + 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"908 - 479 = ?","answers":[{"value":"429", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"271 - 154 = ?","answers":[{"value":"117", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"141 + 135 = ?","answers":[{"value":"276", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"305 - 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"270", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"861 - 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"821", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"783 - 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"720", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"509 - 227 = ?","answers":[{"value":"282", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"196 - 121 = ?","answers":[{"value":"75", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 + 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"52", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"905 - 357 = ?","answers":[{"value":"548", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"738 - 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"711", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"137 + 90 = ?","answers":[{"value":"227", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"806 - 105 = ?","answers":[{"value":"701", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"225 - 118 = ?","answers":[{"value":"107", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"758 - 662 = ?","answers":[{"value":"96", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"909 - 123 = ?","answers":[{"value":"786", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"716 - 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"657", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"683 - 260 = ?","answers":[{"value":"423", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"501 - 349 = ?","answers":[{"value":"152", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"568 - 325 = ?","answers":[{"value":"243", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"197 + 338 = ?","answers":[{"value":"535", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"802 - 331 = ?","answers":[{"value":"471", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"307 + 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"322", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86 + 275 = ?","answers":[{"value":"361", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"902 - 208 = ?","answers":[{"value":"694", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"755 + 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"827", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"284 + 2 = ?","answers":[{"value":"286", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"706 - 297 = ?","answers":[{"value":"409", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"832 - 418 = ?","answers":[{"value":"414", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"129 + 99 = ?","answers":[{"value":"228", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"901 - 184 = ?","answers":[{"value":"717", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"825 - 14 = ?","answers":[{"value":"811", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"822 - 295 = ?","answers":[{"value":"527", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"209 - 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"183", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"259 + 132 = ?","answers":[{"value":"391", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"484 - 321 = ?","answers":[{"value":"163", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"907 - 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"828", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"779 - 733 = ?","answers":[{"value":"46", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"132 + 257 = ?","answers":[{"value":"389", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"703 - 122 = ?","answers":[{"value":"581", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"217 + 166 = ?","answers":[{"value":"383", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"226 + 430 = ?","answers":[{"value":"656", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"300 - 249 = ?","answers":[{"value":"51", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"171 + 431 = ?","answers":[{"value":"602", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"289 + 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"306", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"805 - 152 = ?","answers":[{"value":"653", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"469 + 388 = ?","answers":[{"value":"857", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"533 - 505 = ?","answers":[{"value":"28", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"900 - 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"873", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"875 - 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"857", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"438 - 224 = ?","answers":[{"value":"214", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"707 - 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"655", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"774 + 5 = ?","answers":[{"value":"779", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"754 - 544 = ?","answers":[{"value":"210", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"707 - 177 = ?","answers":[{"value":"530", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 + 374 = ?","answers":[{"value":"381", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"312 + 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"376", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"801 - 256 = ?","answers":[{"value":"545", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"174 + 500 = ?","answers":[{"value":"674", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"274 + 239 = ?","answers":[{"value":"513", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"408 - 2 = ?","answers":[{"value":"406", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"114 + 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"131", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26 + 180 = ?","answers":[{"value":"206", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"800 - 200 = ?","answers":[{"value":"600", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 + 3 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17 + 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"36", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"806 - 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"729", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"414 - 160 = ?","answers":[{"value":"254", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 + 93 = ?","answers":[{"value":"152", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"709 - 98 = ?","answers":[{"value":"611", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"138 + 141 = ?","answers":[{"value":"279", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"772 - 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"702", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103 - 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"78", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 + 12 = ?","answers":[{"value":"15", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"257 + 207 = ?","answers":[{"value":"464", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"903 - 225 = ?","answers":[{"value":"678", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"391 + 322 = ?","answers":[{"value":"713", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"529 + 300 = ?","answers":[{"value":"829", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"904 - 634 = ?","answers":[{"value":"270", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"281 + 408 = ?","answers":[{"value":"689", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"204 + 295 = ?","answers":[{"value":"499", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"608 - 227 = ?","answers":[{"value":"381", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"867 - 255 = ?","answers":[{"value":"612", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"764 + 143 = ?","answers":[{"value":"907", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"907 - 116 = ?","answers":[{"value":"791", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"465 - 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"391", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"10 + 333 = ?","answers":[{"value":"343", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"705 - 170 = ?","answers":[{"value":"535", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"503 + 189 = ?","answers":[{"value":"692", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"46 + 734 = ?","answers":[{"value":"780", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"606 - 109 = ?","answers":[{"value":"497", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"117 + 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"152", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"892 - 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"871", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"800 - 290 = ?","answers":[{"value":"510", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"654 - 430 = ?","answers":[{"value":"224", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"363 + 271 = ?","answers":[{"value":"634", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"402 - 230 = ?","answers":[{"value":"172", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"670 - 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"600", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"843 - 155 = ?","answers":[{"value":"688", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"904 - 155 = ?","answers":[{"value":"749", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"345 + 4 = ?","answers":[{"value":"349", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51 + 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"109", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"902 - 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"822", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"225 - 191 = ?","answers":[{"value":"34", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"478 - 308 = ?","answers":[{"value":"170", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102 - 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"35", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"263 + 372 = ?","answers":[{"value":"635", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"374 + 122 = ?","answers":[{"value":"496", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"906 - 99 = ?","answers":[{"value":"807", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"182 + 282 = ?","answers":[{"value":"464", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"136 + 304 = ?","answers":[{"value":"440", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"907 - 614 = ?","answers":[{"value":"293", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"778 - 8 = ?","answers":[{"value":"770", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 + 154 = ?","answers":[{"value":"159", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"800 - 407 = ?","answers":[{"value":"393", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"815 - 93 = ?","answers":[{"value":"722", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"92 + 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"116", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"506 - 214 = ?","answers":[{"value":"292", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"185 + 713 = ?","answers":[{"value":"898", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"131 + 320 = ?","answers":[{"value":"451", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"700 - 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"642", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"851 - 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"787", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77 + 7 = ?","answers":[{"value":"84", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"902 - 7 = ?","answers":[{"value":"895", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84 + 136 = ?","answers":[{"value":"220", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86 + 185 = ?","answers":[{"value":"271", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"705 - 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"689", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"678 - 517 = ?","answers":[{"value":"161", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"834 - 350 = ?","answers":[{"value":"484", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"800 - 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"754", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"217 - 127 = ?","answers":[{"value":"90", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77 + 304 = ?","answers":[{"value":"381", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"600 - 288 = ?","answers":[{"value":"312", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"441 - 135 = ?","answers":[{"value":"306", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59 + 217 = ?","answers":[{"value":"276", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"800 - 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"737", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"393 + 151 = ?","answers":[{"value":"544", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73 + 382 = ?","answers":[{"value":"455", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"805 - 355 = ?","answers":[{"value":"450", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"820 - 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"798", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"838 - 600 = ?","answers":[{"value":"238", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"700 - 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"656", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"784 + 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"853", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"237 + 504 = ?","answers":[{"value":"741", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"401 - 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"360", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"822 - 103 = ?","answers":[{"value":"719", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"891 - 856 = ?","answers":[{"value":"35", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"904 - 142 = ?","answers":[{"value":"762", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"217 + 275 = ?","answers":[{"value":"492", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"428 + 450 = ?","answers":[{"value":"878", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"501 - 189 = ?","answers":[{"value":"312", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"790 - 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"714", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"874 - 787 = ?","answers":[{"value":"87", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"303 - 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"284", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"472 - 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"429", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 + 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"908 - 713 = ?","answers":[{"value":"195", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"888 - 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"870", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"178 + 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"211", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"902 - 1 = ?","answers":[{"value":"901", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"273 - 9 = ?","answers":[{"value":"264", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103 + 616 = ?","answers":[{"value":"719", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"807 - 538 = ?","answers":[{"value":"269", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"726 - 1 = ?","answers":[{"value":"725", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"772 - 255 = ?","answers":[{"value":"517", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"801 - 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"772", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"472 + 104 = ?","answers":[{"value":"576", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"809 + 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"859", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"907 - 97 = ?","answers":[{"value":"810", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"96 + 105 = ?","answers":[{"value":"201", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"766 - 665 = ?","answers":[{"value":"101", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"801 - 379 = ?","answers":[{"value":"422", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"518 + 338 = ?","answers":[{"value":"856", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"828 + 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"881", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"700 - 129 = ?","answers":[{"value":"571", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"568 + 221 = ?","answers":[{"value":"789", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"418 - 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"382", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"903 - 2 = ?","answers":[{"value":"901", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"854 - 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"815", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"421 - 11 = ?","answers":[{"value":"410", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"201 - 162 = ?","answers":[{"value":"39", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"40 + 856 = ?","answers":[{"value":"896", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"725 - 96 = ?","answers":[{"value":"629", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"806 - 516 = ?","answers":[{"value":"290", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"587 - 275 = ?","answers":[{"value":"312", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"661 - 594 = ?","answers":[{"value":"67", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"702 - 205 = ?","answers":[{"value":"497", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"861 - 156 = ?","answers":[{"value":"705", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"589 - 13 = ?","answers":[{"value":"576", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"702 - 484 = ?","answers":[{"value":"218", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"825 - 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"775", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"282 - 150 = ?","answers":[{"value":"132", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"808 - 221 = ?","answers":[{"value":"587", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"860 - 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"790", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"564 - 299 = ?","answers":[{"value":"265", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"709 - 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"672", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"881 - 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"846", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"757 - 134 = ?","answers":[{"value":"623", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"905 - 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"856", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"894 - 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"836", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"227 + 2 = ?","answers":[{"value":"229", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"802 - 601 = ?","answers":[{"value":"201", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"578 - 158 = ?","answers":[{"value":"420", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"522 + 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"578", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"608 - 511 = ?","answers":[{"value":"97", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"323 - 320 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"521 - 271 = ?","answers":[{"value":"250", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"908 - 86 = ?","answers":[{"value":"822", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"347 - 345 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"252 + 166 = ?","answers":[{"value":"418", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"907 - 14 = ?","answers":[{"value":"893", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107 + 303 = ?","answers":[{"value":"410", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"232 + 531 = ?","answers":[{"value":"763", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"602 - 422 = ?","answers":[{"value":"180", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"601 + 223 = ?","answers":[{"value":"824", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"644 - 625 = ?","answers":[{"value":"19", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"903 - 248 = ?","answers":[{"value":"655", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"302 + 213 = ?","answers":[{"value":"515", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"657 + 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"709", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"706 - 127 = ?","answers":[{"value":"579", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"890 - 435 = ?","answers":[{"value":"455", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15 + 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"86", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"507 - 302 = ?","answers":[{"value":"205", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"773 - 150 = ?","answers":[{"value":"623", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"135 + 96 = ?","answers":[{"value":"231", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"902 - 452 = ?","answers":[{"value":"450", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"825 - 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"797", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68 + 776 = ?","answers":[{"value":"844", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"707 - 8 = ?","answers":[{"value":"699", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"351 - 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"272", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"711 - 2 = ?","answers":[{"value":"709", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"903 - 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"833", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"831 - 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"795", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"268 + 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"317", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"801 - 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"764", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62 + 121 = ?","answers":[{"value":"183", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"875 - 169 = ?","answers":[{"value":"706", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"603 - 181 = ?","answers":[{"value":"422", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"195 + 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"237", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"27 + 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"60", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"609 - 268 = ?","answers":[{"value":"341", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"789 - 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"754", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"164 + 311 = ?","answers":[{"value":"475", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"808 - 351 = ?","answers":[{"value":"457", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"121 + 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"192", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"555 - 531 = ?","answers":[{"value":"24", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"803 - 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"754", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"810 - 104 = ?","answers":[{"value":"706", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"380 + 157 = ?","answers":[{"value":"537", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"604 - 175 = ?","answers":[{"value":"429", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"29 + 3 = ?","answers":[{"value":"32", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"280 - 246 = ?","answers":[{"value":"34", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"706 - 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"674", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"851 - 850 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"287 - 174 = ?","answers":[{"value":"113", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"701 - 85 = ?","answers":[{"value":"616", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"858 - 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"790", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"570 + 154 = ?","answers":[{"value":"724", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"600 - 552 = ?","answers":[{"value":"48", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"44 + 846 = ?","answers":[{"value":"890", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"159 + 130 = ?","answers":[{"value":"289", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"903 - 853 = ?","answers":[{"value":"50", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 + 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"81", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"314 - 263 = ?","answers":[{"value":"51", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"201 - 200 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"196 + 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"213", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74 + 491 = ?","answers":[{"value":"565", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"500 - 216 = ?","answers":[{"value":"284", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"727 - 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"688", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"883 - 468 = ?","answers":[{"value":"415", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"800 - 687 = ?","answers":[{"value":"113", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 + 1 = ?","answers":[{"value":"10", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"481 - 235 = ?","answers":[{"value":"246", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"602 - 159 = ?","answers":[{"value":"443", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"878 - 490 = ?","answers":[{"value":"388", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"568 - 238 = ?","answers":[{"value":"330", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"901 - 142 = ?","answers":[{"value":"759", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45 + 249 = ?","answers":[{"value":"294", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"317 + 485 = ?","answers":[{"value":"802", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"402 - 279 = ?","answers":[{"value":"123", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"868 - 159 = ?","answers":[{"value":"709", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"898 - 98 = ?","answers":[{"value":"800", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"702 - 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"638", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"825 - 303 = ?","answers":[{"value":"522", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"147 + 293 = ?","answers":[{"value":"440", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"701 - 624 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"760 - 94 = ?","answers":[{"value":"666", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"326 + 317 = ?","answers":[{"value":"643", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"606 - 186 = ?","answers":[{"value":"420", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100 + 488 = ?","answers":[{"value":"588", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"577 - 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"522", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"901 - 14 = ?","answers":[{"value":"887", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"43 + 170 = ?","answers":[{"value":"213", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"145 + 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"187", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"709 - 608 = ?","answers":[{"value":"101", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"119 + 376 = ?","answers":[{"value":"495", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"431 - 88 = ?","answers":[{"value":"343", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"904 - 211 = ?","answers":[{"value":"693", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"791 - 107 = ?","answers":[{"value":"684", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"870 - 112 = ?","answers":[{"value":"758", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"700 - 190 = ?","answers":[{"value":"510", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"561 - 430 = ?","answers":[{"value":"131", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"173 + 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"213", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"801 - 631 = ?","answers":[{"value":"170", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 + 1 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"225 + 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"288", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"905 - 54 = ?","answers":[{"value":"851", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"691 + 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"733", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"574 + 93 = ?","answers":[{"value":"667", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"907 - 115 = ?","answers":[{"value":"792", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"363 + 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"391", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"353 + 129 = ?","answers":[{"value":"482", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"503 - 204 = ?","answers":[{"value":"299", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"414 + 242 = ?","answers":[{"value":"656", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"172 - 101 = ?","answers":[{"value":"71", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"906 - 542 = ?","answers":[{"value":"364", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"529 + 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"597", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58 + 315 = ?","answers":[{"value":"373", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"800 - 556 = ?","answers":[{"value":"244", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"438 + 14 = ?","answers":[{"value":"452", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"879 - 342 = ?","answers":[{"value":"537", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"708 - 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"668", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"754 - 684 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"787 - 287 = ?","answers":[{"value":"500", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
